Guide to the David Hamburg papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Correspondence
  - Subseries III.1: Individuals
    - Coleman, John, 1982-1982 (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Coller, Barry, 2000- (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Comer, James, 1983-2000 (Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Conger, John J., 1978-1982 (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Connor, W. Robert, 1991-1995 (Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Constine, Ronald, 1976-1976 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Cooney, James, 1983-1983 (Box 257, Folder 16)
    - Cooper, Theodore, 1980-1988 (Box 257, Folder 17)
    - Corbally, Marguerite, 1985-1985 (Box 257, Folder 18)
    - Cor-Cry (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Corning, Peter, 1971-1985 (Box 257, Folder 19)
    - Corrigan, Gerald, 1992- (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Corson, Samuel A., 1988-1989 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Cortes, Ernesto, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Cortese, Anthony, 1993- (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Couper, Richard W., 1981-1983 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Craig, Catherine, 1971-1985 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Cranshaw, Ralph, 1980-1986 (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Cranston, Alan, 1987-2000 (Box 258, Folder 9-10)
    - Cremin, Larry, 1982-1988 (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Crocker, John, 1972-1977 (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Cronkite, Walter, 1994-1998 (Box 258, Folder 13)
    - Cue-Cze (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Cuthbertson, Kenneth, 1977-1984 (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Czeisler, Charles, 1982-1983 (Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Daddario, Emilio, 1975-1984 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Da-Di (Box 263, Folder 5-6)
    - Dainton, Frederick, 1985- (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - D'Amato, Alphonse M., 1982- (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Danforth, William, 1977-1988 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Dans, Peter, 1980-1987 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Darnell, Jonathan, 1990- (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Davidson, Charles S., 1983-1985 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Davidson, Ezra C., 1990-1997 (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Bernard D., 1980-1982 (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Davis, John Marcell, 1983-1990 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Karen, 1976-1999 (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Kenneth L., 1982-1999 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Martin, 1984-1985 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Days, Drew S. III, 1990-1993 (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - Dayton, Bruce B., 1985-1989 (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - De (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - de Zalduondo, Barbara O., 1975-1994 (Box 236, Folder 11-12)
    - Dean, Howard, 1995-1998 (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - Delbanco, Thomas L., 1978-1992 (Box 235, Folder 17)
    - DeLeon, Candido A., 1990- (Box 235, Folder 18)
    - Dement, William, 1985-2000 (Box 235, Folder 19-20)
    - Dement, William, 1978-1996 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Demlo, Linda, 1979-1985 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Deng, Francis, 1991-1998 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Deuschle, Kurt, 1983-1984 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Deutsch, Morton, 1986-1998 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Devlin-Fotz, David, 1988-1996 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Devore, Irven, 1974-2000 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - DeWind, Andrew, 1983-1997 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Dews, Peter, 1979-1982 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Dewson, James H., 1973-1978 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Diamond, Larry, 1993-1999 (Box 237, Folder 1-3)
    - Dimsdale, Joel E., 1972-1999 (Box 237, Folder 4-5)
    - Dingell, Deborah I., 1992-1993 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Dinkins, David N.(New York City Mayor), 1990-1995 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Djerassi, Carl, 1979-1994 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Do (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Doering, Charles, 1976-1991 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Donahue, Thomas R., 1993-1997 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Dornbusch, Sanford, 1975-1996 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Dorwart, Robert, 1984-1995 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Downey, D. Chris, 1990-1992 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Downey, Thomas, 1984-1995 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Dr (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Draper, William H. III, 1989-1992 (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Drell, Sidney, 1982-1999 (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - du Pont, Pierre S. IV, 1983-1983 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Duffey, Joseph, 1990-1997 (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Dugard, John, 1984-1985 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Dukakis, Michael, 1982-1998 (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Dulaney, Peggy, 1980-1996 (Box 262, Folder 12-13)
    - Dunham, E. Alden, 1984-1992 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Dunlop, John, 1979-1998 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Durenberger, Dave, 1989-1992 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Dw-Dy (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Ea-Ed (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Eagleburger, Lawrence S., 1985-1994 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Ebert, James, 1982-1984 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Ebert, Robert, 1979-1990 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Ed-Ek (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Edelman, Marian Wright, 1991-1997 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Edelman, Peter B, 1989-1996 (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Edes, Nik B., 1986-1987 (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Edwards, Mickey, 1992-1994 (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - Ehrhardt, Anne A., 1973-1990 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Ehrlich, Paul, 1977-1984 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Ehrlich, Thomas, 1987-1995 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Eisenberg, Leon, 1978-1998 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhower, Susan, 1989-1998 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Ekbladh, David, 1996-2001 (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - El-Etz (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Eliasson, Jan, 1996-2000 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Elliot, Glen R., 1977-1988 (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Elliott, Delbert S., 1991-1995 (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Ellwood, David, 1988-1998 (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Engelhardt, Sara, 1987-1998 (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Enthoven, Alain, 1978-1982 (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Epstein, Franklin, 1975-1982 (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - Erlenmyer-Kimling, L (Niki), 1978-1978 (Box 265, Folder 14)
    - Etheredge, Lloyd, 1983-2000 (Box 266, Folder 2-3)
    - Etz-Ey (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Evans, Eli, 1979-1989 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Evans, Gareth, 1997-2000 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Evans, John R., 1978-2000 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Ezekiel, Raphael, 1984-1999 (Box 266, Folder 7-8)
    - Fa (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Falco, Mathea, 1986-1998 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Falcon, Walter P., 1991-1999 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Falkner, Frank, 1978-1996 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Fanton, Jonathan F., 1982-1993 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Farquhar, John, 1978-1995 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Fauci, Anthony S., 1988-1996 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Fe (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Feinberg, Richard E., 1992-1993 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Felzenberg, Al, 1994-1994 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Ferrari, Frank, 1985-1993 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Fi (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Fielding, Jonathan, 1979-1992 (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Finberg, Alan, 1985-1995 (Box 269, Folder 9)
    - Finberg, Barbara, 1985-2000 (Box 269, Folder 10-11)
    - Fineberg, Harvey, 1981-2000 (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - Fisher, Richard, 1983-1999 (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - Fisher, Roger, 1983-1985 (Box 270, Folder 1-2)
    - Fiske, Ted, 1984-1996 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Fl (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Fleishman, Joel L., 1986-1997 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Fo (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Foege, William, 1985-1997 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Fonda, Jane, 1998-2000 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1988-1993 (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Forman, Shepard, 1996-1998 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Forsham, Ann, 1977-1978 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Fossey, Diane, 1970-1980 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Foster, Henry, 1994-1996 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Fra (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Frankenhauser, Marianne, 1971-2000 (Box 270, Folder 12-13)
    - Fre (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1992-1998 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1988-1996 (Box 271, Folder 1-2)
    - Frederickson, Donald, 1979-1998 (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Freedman, Danny, 1983-1983 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Freymond, Jean, 1993-1994 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Fri (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Fro-Futt (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - Frowick, Robert H., 1989-1989 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - Frye, Alton, 1993-1995 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Fuchs, Victor R., 1981-1992 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Furlaud, Richard M, 1991-1992 (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Fuster, Valentin, 1999-1999 (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Futter, Ellen V., 1993-2000 (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Ga (Box 289, Folder 8-9)
    - Gaither, Jim, 1977-1999 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Galvin, Jack, 1993-1996 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Garber, Joseph, 1991-1997 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Gardell, Bertil, 1977-1980 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Garden, Timothy, 1997-1997 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Gardner, David Pierrpont, 1985-1988 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Gardner, John, 1980-2000 (Box 223, Folder 7-8)
    - Gardner, Richard, 1990-1996 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Garrison, Clare, 1999- (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Garrison, Jim, 1993-1998 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Garrison, Lloyd, 1983-1984 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Ge (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Gebre-Christos, Berhane (Ethiopian Ambassador to Europe), 1999- (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Gelb, Leslie, 1986-2000 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Gelhorn, Alfred, 1989-1989 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - George, Alexander, 1958-2002 (Box 224, Folder 1-6)
    - Gershman, Carl, 1993-1998 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Getty, Gordon and Ann, 1991-1999 (Box 225, Folder 2-4)
    - Getty, Peter, 1983-1989 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Gh-Gi (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Gibbons, John, 1984-1998 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Gibbs, James L., 1993-1997 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Gibbs, Jewelle, 1972-1994 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Gilbert, Ellen, 1997- (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Gillin, Christian, 1980-2000 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader, 1994-1994 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Ginzberg, Eli, 1983-1999 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Giuliani, Rudolph, 1995-1997 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Glaser, Robert, 1979-2001 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Gleason, Herbert, 1979-1986 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Glenn, John (Astronaut, senator from Ohio), 1983-1988 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Gl-Go (Box 290, Folder 1-2)
    - Glickman, Steve (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Gloster, John S., 1985-1990 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - Godber, Sir George, 1976-1981 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Godsell, Robert, 1988-1998 (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Goldbeck, Willis, 1977-1981 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Goldberger, Marvin, 1980-1987 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - Goldberger, Robert, 1983-1984 (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - Golden, William, 1995-1998 (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - Golden, William, 1982-1995 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Goldmark, Peter, 1988-1992 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Goldstein, Avram, 1968-1998 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Goldstein, Joshua, 1985-1991 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Goldstein, Naomi, 1990-2000 (Box 227, Folder 5-8)
    - Goldstein, Naomi, 1988-2000 (Box 286, Folder 1-2)
    - Goldstone, Richard J., 1993-1998 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Gonda, Thomas, 1976-1987 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Goodall, Jane, 1957-2000 (Box 286, Folder 5-6)
    - Goodfield, June, 1983-1991 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Goodpaster, Andrew, 1991-1998 (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Goodwin, Frederick K., 1992-1995 (Box 286, Folder 9)
    - Goodwin, Neva, 1986-2000 (Box 286, Folder 10)
    - Gorbachev, Mikhail S., 1992-1999 (Box 287, Folder 1-4)
    - Gore, Albert Jr., 1985-2000 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Gore, Tipper, 1995-1996 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Gorham, William, 1982-1995 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Goslin, David, 1982-1986 (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - Gotbaum, Betsy, 1983-1983 (Box 287, Folder 9)
    - Gotbaum, Victor, 1989-1990 (Box 287, Folder 10)
    - Gr (Box 290, Folder 3-5)
    - Graham, Katherine, 1984-1998 (Box 287, Folder 11)
    - Grandy, Fred, 1994-1994 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Grant, James, 1989-1995 (Box 287, Folder 12)
    - Gray, Bradford H., 1988-1996 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - Gray, Hanna, 1983-1997 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - Green, Lawrence, 1983-1984 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Greenberg, Melanie, 2003- (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Greene, Richard W., 1983-1985 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Greengard, Paul, 1984-1994 (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - Greenstock, Jeremy, 2001- (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - Gregorian, Vartan, 1988-2000 (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - Grele, Roland, 1999-2000 (Box 288, Folder 12)
    - Grinker, Roy Jr., 1983-1998 (Box 288, Folder 14)
    - Grinker, Roy Sr., 1976-1993 (Box 288, Folder 13)
    - Grisi, Jeanmarie, 1995-1999 (Box 288, Folder 15)
    - Grisi, Jeanmarie, 1984-1995 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Grobstein, Clifford, 1980-1982 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Growald, Eileen, Rockefeller, 1983-1997 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Guggenhime, David, 1980-1994 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Guggenhime, Richard Sr., 1977-1982 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Gu-Gy (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Gunther, Gerald, 1979-1980 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Gwatkin, Davidson, 1983-1986 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Ha (Box 276, Folder 1-4)
    - Haber, Paul, 1983-1983 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Haber, Suzanne, 1974-1996 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Hagemann, Hans and Ivan, 1992-1992 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Haggerty, Robert J, 1977-1996 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Hallen, Philip B., 1983-1984 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - Halperin, Morton, 2001- (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Halpern, Charles, 1991-1996 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - Hamburg, Roger, 1976-1996 (Box 291, Folder 9-11)
    - Hamilton, James B., 1985-1994 (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Hamilton, Lee, 1987-2001 (Box 291, Folder 13-17)
    - Hamilton, Ruth Simms, 1982-1998 (Box 291, Folder 18-19)
    - Hammad, Aleya, 1993-1994 (Box 292, Folder 1-2)
    - Hanna, Paul R., 1977-1983 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Harding, Robert S.O., 1975-1979 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Hardman, John, 1998-2001 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Hardy, Gladys Chang, 1983-1984 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Harkavy, Oscar, 1985-1990 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Harkin, Tom, 1985-1997 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Harlow, Harry F., 1971-1977 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Harman, David, 1984- (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Harriman, Pamela C., 1984-1992 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Harris, Irving, 1978-2000 (Box 292, Folder 12-17)
    - Harris, Louis, 1985-1992 (Box 292, Folder 18)
    - Harris, Patricia, 1979-1992 (Box 292, Folder 19)
    - Harris, Robie H., 1995- (Box 292, Folder 20)
    - Harris, William W., 1970-1992 (Box 292, Folder 21)
    - Harrison, Anna, 1982- (Box 292, Folder 22)
    - Hartley, L Howard, 1980-1980 (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Harvey, A. McGehee, 1984-1984 (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Haskins, Caryl P., 1983-1998 (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Hauser, Rita, 1990-2000 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Hays, Sarah, 1974-1981 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - He (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Hearing, Brenda, 1996-2001 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Hechinger, Fred, 1982-1996 (Box 272, Folder 7-9)
    - Hector, Louis J., 1982-2000 (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Heffner, Richard D., 1995-1999 (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Heffner, Richard D., 1992-1996 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - He-Hi (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Heidrich, Grant, 1972-1988 (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Hein, Karen K., 1987-2000 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Heinz, John, 1985-1991 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Heinz, Teresa, 1985-1996 (Box 273, Folder 5-6)
    - Heller, H. Craig, 1993-1998 (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Herskovitz, Jean, 1990-1996 (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Herz, Marvin, 1976-1986 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M., 1982-1998 (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - Hesselbein, Frances, 1987-1989 (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - Hi (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Hiatt, Howard, 1979-1994 (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Higginbotham, A Leon, 1984-1996 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Hinde, Robert, 1970-2000 (Box 274, Folder 3-4)
    - Hinkle, Lawrence, 1981-1982 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Ho (Box 277, Folder 3-5)
    - Hoffman, Stanley, 1983-1983 (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Hofstadter, Douglas R., 1976-1994 (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Hofstadter, Laura, 1976-1978 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Hofstadter, Robert, 1977-1990 (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - Holbrooke, Richard, 1998-2001 (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - Holder, Idalia, 1992-1999 (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - Holdren, John, 1998- (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Holl, Jane, 1992-2000 (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Holman, M. Carl, 1985-1988 (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Hood, David, 1983-1993 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Hornbeck, David W., 1989-1996 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Horowitz, Larry, 1978-1988 (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Howson, Christopher, 1995-1997 (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Hu (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Hubbard, W.N. Jr, 1979-1982 (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Hufstedler, Shirley M., 1984-1996 (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Hunt, Albert, 1999-1999 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Hunt, James B. Jr., 1985-2001 (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Hunter, Carrie, 1977-2000 (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Hunter-Gault, Charlayne, 1995-1997 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Hutt, Peter B., 1977-1984 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Huttenback, Robert A, 1984-1993 (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - I (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Igleheart, John K., 1983-1983 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Ikenberry, Stanley, 1996-1996 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Inouye, Daniel (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Isbister, James D., 1977-1977 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Isham, Heyward, ND- (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Ja (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - Jackson, Anthony W., 1990-1997 (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - Jacobs, Klaus, 1996-2000 (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - Janis, Irving, 1983-1990 (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - Jaramillo, Mari-Luci, 1983-1990 (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - Je (Box 279, Folder 7)
    - Jennison, M. Harry, 1983-1987 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Jessor, Richard, 1991-1998 (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - Jo (Box 279, Folder 8-9)
    - Johnson, Julie, 1971-1992 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Boisfeuillet, 1982-1988 (Box 278, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Judith E., 1986-1998 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Judith Miller, 1984-1990 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Joseph, James A., 1984-1998 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Joseph, Stephen, 1983-1990 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Ju (Box 279, Folder 10)
    - Judd, Lewis, 1982-2000 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Ka (Box 284, Folder 23)
    - Ka (Box 293, Folder 1-2)
    - Kagan, Sharon Lynn, 1992-1996 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Kagen, Jerome, 1984-1998 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Kahn, Arlene, 1985-1986 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Kane, William M., 1988-1988 (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Kaplan, Berton H., 1973-1993 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Kaplan, Helene, 1981-2000 (Box 280, Folder 6-7)
    - Kaplan, Ronne, 1982-1982 (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Kaplan, Sue, 1989-1994 (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Kappner, Augusta Souza, 1995-2000 (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - Karl, Barry, 1983-1983 (Box 280, Folder 11)
    - Kase, Nathan, 1985-1997 (Box 280, Folder 12)
    - Kassebaum, Nancy, 1985-1987 (Box 280, Folder 13)
    - Kassoff, Alan, 1993-2000 (Box 280, Folder 14)
    - Kassoff, Alan, 1991-1997 (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Katchadourian, Herant, 1986-1995 (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Katz, Israel, 1983-1985 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Kea - Kel (Box 293, Folder 3-4)
    - Kean, Thomas, 1985-1998 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Kearns, David J., 1987-1994 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Kelly, Marcy, 1990-1998 (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - Kem-Kez (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Kennan, George, 1987-1989 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Donald, 1980-2000 (Box 281, Folder 8-9)
    - Kennedy, Edward, 1976-2000 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Kennedy, Edward Jr, 1991-1993 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy, Jeanne, 1976-1998 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Paul, 1994-2000 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Keohane, Nannerl, 1983-1995 (Box 282, Folder 5)
    - Kerry, John, 1986-2000 (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - Kety, Seymour S., 1977-1982 (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - Keynan, Alex, 1981-1998 (Box 282, Folder 8)
    - Kh - Kn (Box 293, Folder 6-7)
    - Kiely, Mary L., 1993-1998 (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - Kiely, Mary L., 1981-1993 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Killilea, Marie, 1979-1992 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - King, Mary, 1979-1993 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - King, Susan, 1999- (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Kipke, Michele D., 1998-2000 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Klein, Laura Colin, 1994-1995 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Kleinman, Arthur, 1981-1999 (Box 283, Folder 7-9)
    - Klerman, Lorraine, 1991-1998 (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - Klingenstein, Frederick A., 1984-2000 (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - Knapp, Dorothy, 1987-2000 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Knerr, Jennifer, 2000- (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Knobil, Ernest, 1985-2000 (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Knowles, John H, 1976-1979 (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Ko - Kz (Box 294, Folder 1-3)
    - Koenig, Heather, 1999- (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Kofol, Anne, 1999-2000 (Box 284, Folder 6-7)
    - Kohl, Herb, 1989-1992 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Kokoshin, Andrei, 1992-1996 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - Konnor, Melvin, 1975-1993 (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - Koop, C. Everett, 1992-1992 (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - Koppel, Ted, 1986-1999 (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - Koshland, Daniel E. Jr, 1986-1992 (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Kotulak, Ronald, 1993- (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - Kozyrev, Andrei, undated- (Box 284, Folder 15)
    - Kraemer, Helena, 1975-1993 (Box 284, Folder 16)
    - Krause, Richard, 1977-1980 (Box 284, Folder 17)
    - Krauthammer, Charles, 1979-2000 (Box 284, Folder 18)
    - Kreisler, Harry, 1998-ND (Box 284, Folder 21-22)
    - Krents, Milton, 1988-1993 (Box 284, Folder 19)
    - Krieger, Dorothy T., 1980-1984 (Box 284, Folder 20)
    - La (Box 297, Folder 17)
    - La (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Lageman, Ellen Condliffe, 1990-1998 (Box 294, Folder 4-5)
    - Lake, Anthony, 1994-1995 (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Lancaster, Jane B., 1981-1982 (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Landau, Ralph, 1989- (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Landrigan, Philip J., 1990-1999 (Box 294, Folder 9-11)
    - Lane, Neal, 1994-2001 (Box 294, Folder 12)
    - Lang, Eugene, 1992-1996 (Box 294, Folder 13)
    - Lang, Janet M., 1989- (Box 294, Folder 14)
    - Langfitt, Thomas W., M.D., 1987-1994 (Box 294, Folder 15)
    - Lansing, Dorothy I., 1986-1996 (Box 294, Folder 16-17)
    - Lapidus, Gail, 1990-1995 (Box 294, Folder 18)
    - Lashof, Joyce C., M.D., 1984-1998 (Box 294, Folder 19)
    - Lawrence, Robert S., M.D., 1979-1995 (Box 294, Folder 20)
    - Lawton, Steve, 1980-1987 (Box 294, Folder 21)
    - Lazarus, Richard, 1976-1979 (Box 294, Folder 22)
    - Le (Box 298, Folder 2-4)
    - Leaf, Alexander, 1978-1996 (Box 294, Folder 23-24)
    - Lederberg, Joshua, 1967-2000 (Box 295, Folder 1-5)
    - Lederberg, Marguerite, 1992-1997 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Lederman, Leon M., 1986-1998 (Box 295, Folder 7-8)
    - Lee, Paul B., 1993-1994 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Philip R., 1977-1998 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Lees, Martin, 1993-2000 (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - Lele, Uma, 1993-1994 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Lenfant, Claude, M.D. (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Lenven, Ann R., 1982-1986 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Lester, Patricia J. (Trisha), 1984-2000 (Box 295, Folder 14-15)
    - Levenson, Ruth A, 1983-1983 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Levi, Lenart, 1975-1993 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Levin, Barbara, 1992-1992 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Levin, Carl, 1983-1998 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Levin, Richard, 1993-2000 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Michael, 1990-1997 (Box 296, Folder 7-8)
    - Levy, Jack, 1998- (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - Lewis, Anthony, 1986-1998 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Lewis, Charles, 1978-1979 (Box 296, Folder 11)
    - Lewis, Douglas B., 1974-1980 (Box 296, Folder 12)
    - Lewis, John W., 1983-1989 (Box 296, Folder 13)
    - Lewis, Samuel W., 1989-1993 (Box 296, Folder 14)
    - Li (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Lieberman, Joseph, 1991-2000 (Box 296, Folder 15)
    - Lindzey, Gardner, 1976-1986 (Box 296, Folder 16)
    - Linowitz, Sol, 1982-1998 (Box 296, Folder 17)
    - Lipkin, Mack, 1980-1986 (Box 296, Folder 18)
    - Lipp, Martin, 1977-1980 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Lippin, Richard A., 1995-1996 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Lipton, Morris, 1977-1983 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Ll-Lo (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Lloyd, R. MacAllister, 1983-1983 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Loeb, Susan, 1977-1978 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Long, Beverly, 1989-1995 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Lowe, George, 1983-1983 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Lowrance, William W., 1983-1984 (Box 297, Folder 8)